When people are afraid of you... you can do anything. Remember that.
The Krays is a drama, crime, history film directed by Peter Medak.
Twins Ronnie and Reggie Kray are raised in east London, under the
influence of their hateful but doting mother Violet.
As they grow up, Ronnie's violent nature takes over,
and Reggie follows his brother's lead.
The two become notorious crime lords who rule over the East End club scene.
But at the height of their power, the brothers veer into different lives, giving the
older crime bosses a chance to reclaim what the Krays took from them.
Ronald Kray, played by Gary Kemp.
Reggie Kray, played by Martin Kemp.
Violet Kray, played by Billie Whitelaw.
Jack 'The Hat' McVitie, played by Tom Bell.
Rose, played by Susan Fleetwood.
May, played by Charlotte Cornwell.
The Krays is a 1990 British biographical crime
drama film directed by Peter Medak.
The film is based on the lives and crimes of the British gangster twins
Ronald and Reginald Kray, often referred to as The Krays.
The film stars Billie Whitelaw, Tom Bell, and real-life brothers (although not twins)
Gary and Martin Kemp, both of whom were members of the band Spandau Ballet.
The film explores themes of gangster, based on
true story, twins, 1960s, gay theme.
The tone is dark and emotional.